 [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1000' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 1111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010",
      "B) 1100",
      "C) 1001",
      "D) 1111"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0110' to Binary.",
    "answer": "A) 0100",
    "options": [
      "A) 0100",
      "B) 0110",
      "C) 0011",
      "D) 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1101' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 1001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1011",
      "B) 1111",
      "C) 1100",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0101' to Binary.",
    "answer": "C) 0110",
    "options": [
      "A) 0111",
      "B) 0101",
      "C) 0110",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1011' to Binary.",
    "answer": "B) 1101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100",
      "B) 1101",
      "C) 1010",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0011' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 0010",
    "options": [
      "A) 0101",
      "B) 0110",
      "C) 0001",
      "D) 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1110' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 1011",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001",
      "B) 1000",
      "C) 1101",
      "D) 1011"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0001' to Binary.",
    "answer": "A) 0001",
    "options": [
      "A) 0001",
      "B) 0011",
      "C) 0100",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1001' to Binary.",
    "answer": "B) 1110",
    "options": [
      "A) 1101",
      "B) 1110",
      "C) 1000",
      "D) 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0111' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 0010",
      "B) 1101",
      "C) 0110",
      "D) 0101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray code '1001 0001' to Binary.",
    "answer": "C) 1110 0001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010 0011",
      "B) 1001 1000",
      "C) 1110 0001",
      "D) 1101 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray code '1100 1100' to Binary.",
    "answer": "B) 1000 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 0010",
      "B) 1000 1000",
      "C) 1101 1011",
      "D) 1111 1100"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray code '1010 1010' to Binary.",
    "answer": "A) 1100 1100",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100 1100",
      "B) 1010 0101",
      "C) 1101 0101",
      "D) 1001 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray code '1111 0000' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 1010 0000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100 1111",
      "B) 1110 0011",
      "C) 1010 1010",
      "D) 1010 0000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray code '0000 1111' to Binary.",
    "answer": "C) 0000 1010",
    "options": [
      "A) 0011 1100",
      "B) 0001 0010",
      "C) 0000 1010",
      "D) 0011 1011"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0101 0101' to Binary.",
    "answer": "A) 0110 0110",
    "options": [
      "A) 0110 0110",
      "B) 1010 1010",
      "C) 1001 1001",
      "D) 1110 0011"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1100 1100' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 1000 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100 1100",
      "B) 1010 0101",
      "C) 1101 1011",
      "D) 1000 1000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1001 0001' to Binary.",
    "answer": "B) 1110 0001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1000 0011",
      "B) 1110 0001",
      "C) 1111 1111",
      "D) 1010 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '1111 0000' to Binary.",
    "answer": "C) 1010 0000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1111 1100",
      "B) 1100 1100",
      "C) 1010 0000",
      "D) 1011 1111"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Gray Code '0000 1111' to Binary.",
    "answer": "D) 0000 1010",
    "options": [
      "A) 0000 1111",
      "B) 0011 1100",
      "C) 0010 0001",
      "D) 0000 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1010' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "B) 1111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001",
      "B) 1111",
      "C) 1011",
      "D) 1100"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0110' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "D) 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 0111",
      "B) 0011",
      "C) 0100",
      "D) 0101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1100' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "A) 1010",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010",
      "B) 1101",
      "C) 1110",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1001' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 1101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010",
      "B) 1000",
      "C) 1101",
      "D) 1111"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0001' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "A) 0001",
    "options": [
      "A) 0001",
      "B) 0010",
      "C) 0100",
      "D) 0111"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1110' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "D) 1001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1111",
      "B) 0110",
      "C) 1011",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0101' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "B) 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100",
      "B) 0111",
      "C) 0011",
      "D) 0100"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1011' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 1110",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010",
      "B) 0110",
      "C) 1110",
      "D) 1000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0000' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "A) 0000",
    "options": [
      "A) 0000",
      "B) 1000",
      "C) 0010",
      "D) 0101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1111' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1101",
      "B) 1011",
      "C) 1000",
      "D) 1110"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1000 1010' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 1100 1111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010 1100",
      "B) 1000 1101",
      "C) 1100 1111",
      "D) 1110 0110"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1111 0000' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "B) 1000 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1110 1000",
      "B) 1000 1000",
      "C) 1000 1000",
      "D) 1111 0000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1010 1010' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "A) 1111 1111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1111 1111",
      "B) 1100 1100",
      "C) 1011 0101",
      "D) 1000 0001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1101 1010' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "D) 1011 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1100 1011",
      "B) 1111 1111",
      "C) 1001 1001",
      "D) 1011 0111"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0000 1111' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 0000 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 0011 1100",
      "B) 0010 0011",
      "C) 0000 1000",
      "D) 0011 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1001 1011' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "B) 1101 0110",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010 1101",
      "B) 1101 0110",
      "C) 1110 0011",
      "D) 1000 1101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0110 1110' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "A) 0101 1001",
    "options": [
      "A) 0101 1001",
      "B) 0110 1101",
      "C) 0011 0111",
      "D) 0101 0101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1010 0101' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "C) 1111 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1000 1010",
      "B) 1011 1001",
      "C) 1111 0111",
      "D) 1100 1000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '1100 0011' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "D) 1010 0010",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 1100",
      "B) 1111 1100",
      "C) 1000 1101",
      "D) 1010 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Binary '0101 0101' to Gray Code.",
    "answer": "B) 0111 1111",
    "options": [
      "A) 0011 0010",
      "B) 0111 1111",
      "C) 0101 0100",
      "D) 0110 1011"
    ]
  }
]